How far would you go for love?
Fetching Cody is a comedy, drama, fantasy film directed by David Ray.
Art, a drug-addicted dealer and hustler, arrives at his girlfriend
Cody's apartment to find that she has overdosed on heroin.
He tries to fix things by traveling back in time in
an attempt to prevent her death.
Art, played by Jay Baruchel.
Cody, played by Sarah Lind.
Harvey, played by Jim Byrnes.
Holden, played by Lucas Blaney.
Sudden, played by Neil Denis.
David Helmet Yar, played by Liam McGuigan.
Fetching Cody is a 2005 Canadian drama/science-fiction
film, written and directed by David Ray.
The film is set in Vancouver's Downtown Eastside and features
local drag queen Robert Kaiser in a supporting role.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.